I want to tell my story of game B
because I hope somebody gets something
out of it
so for the last few years long before I
found game B I thought I had a
world-changing
project and I still think it's a
world-changing project hence the name of
this channel but I also struggle with my
health and with disabilities and I have
a lot of limitations on my time on my
energy on my finances on a lot
I have neurological issues both that I
was born with and acquired I have a lot
going on and so as on disability in a
dark place but I now call Kelton
Caterpillar GU and from that space
I couldn't get my life in order but I
somehow was able to figure out how we
get the world in order so like I
couldn't make a meal but I could figure
out an entire food system and in doing
there was something that emerged that
was like this thing is so powerful I
can't not get it out into the world and
yet it couldn't look like what I now
call game a like I couldn't edit a video
properly
I couldn't create a explainer video like
other things and so all I could do is
put it out there to the best of my
ability so I joined Twitter hoping to
get 10,000 followers so I could put a
still stuck on 10,000 so I could put out
a crowdfunding campaign I'm at 3,000 I
never get into 10,000 but going on
Twitter I encountered months apart
Remzi who has his project common planet
and Nicole who has her project the
transition and I remember being so
grateful finding these other people who
were doing something similar out in the
world and that was exactly why it was on
Twitter and then I actually discovered a
stream yard which was streamed onto
YouTube and there was something about
this technology
they broke something open in my brain
and all of a sudden I had the
for the idea Cafe which is its own
YouTube channel and I'm like I'm gonna
go live every Friday at noon it was
actually Lebanon then live every Friday
at this specific time I called it fix
our world Friday and I'm just gonna
answer questions about this big
world-changing idea which by the way is
basically a technological cooperative
that we all own together and run
together that empowers us with all the
tools we need to live our best lives
without having power over us but because
I wasn't able to make our white pages I
want to simple to explain it in a way I
wasn't able to make an explainer video I
had to get it out there to the best of
my ability because it was too big not to
and in so doing came up with came in
contact with renze then for September
September 11th was our first idea cafe
we did it on September 11 where we were
that day and then I had my first live
broadcast scheduled for that Friday on
this channel and right beforehand I
think like two hours beforehand did it
started
Remzi mentioned game B have you heard
about it no I haven't well we're on a
call right he's like there's no there's
a call right now and there was something
about that I was like yep and I jumped
on people are introducing themselves and
so I was like looking up what game B was
well trying to participate in a
conversation about game B and they had
this beautiful idea of a game B coffee
shop on zoom anyone could just pop into
and have a conversation about and that
hadn't of itself I was so excited by
finding Remzi Nicole can you imagine
having his face that I could come to any
time and talk about world saving ideas
yes please and then I listened to
Daniels burgers and war on
sense-making well I went for a walk and
did a video on that it was just like
everything was just more language around
what I've been trying to create and now
head language for I was like oh so
people don't like it when I say I'm
gonna dismantle capitalism but if this
is game and we're creating game B that's
much better language is easier to
understand and it doesn't trigger people
in the same way but I also very much
came into the game B space what they
like I know how we create game B with
the technology cooperative and people
who were already like we tried that I'd
like you haven't you tried a technology
project that's not the same thing and I
couldn't communicate the vision properly
to the best of my liking and it made me
show up in a weird way because both I
was desperate I was like Georgia
Stanhope like changing this is and I was
so excited to find people and at the
same time there was that worry of like
well what if they kick me out what if it
didn't show up in the right way and I
did just keep showing up and keep trying
new things and kept and I oh yes I know
how to crate game B I know how we create
can be as obnoxious as that is I don't
know if I can say that I don't now I can
say that I have my version and that's
actually perfect and it isn't about one
version to move forward it's about us
all having our own vision of moving bard
but look out to there so then I've tried
so many things within this space trying
to exid I found people in the coffee
shop rich you interviewed me about my
project that was amazing every time I
came up with an obstacle there was
somebody to reach out to to help me with
it I had conversations with Jordan Hall
and when I didn't understand
cryptocurrency was critical of it export
or had a conversation with me
people on Twitter found he had
conversation I've had hundreds of hours
of conversations about and from with
game B people I had an idea rather early
I think it was late September early
October for a citizen assembly like
entity where you meet every four hours
ask questions you get to you a number
but the whatever that's gonna get to in
these nodes it fell by the wayside it
was too complex for the space there
weren't enough people for it to work
anyway but I learned that failures
actually its own learning thing and
crickets is fine if you get crickets
from something it's it's still more
information and I actually don't
remember how we met Bentley exactly as
far as maybe I posted something in the
space but I remember meeting him and
being like kindred spirit and we moved
forward with together tech like yes I
also want to technological cooperative
we started I think I did Cafe was our
first project more like we'll move
forward with it until we kind of come to
a stall and together Tech has
transformed into something that honors
the space of game be everything we all
have this frustration that we had our
own world
safety and idea whether it was a one
project or this overarching utopia that
we wanted people to come on board for
and yet none of us were willing to give
up our own vision and none of us are
willing to give up our own project and
so own that and like so together Tech
was born which is the game B projects
and people can bring their project and
we can create all new and solutions
together it's been through several
iterations and it's still evolving we
did project raisins
they were very popular but there were
more people interested in participating
as the project lead to have someone come
and raise your project and to raise
other people's projects which was just
an hour focused crowd crowd focused
discussion say crowd raising them I like
using the record raising clearly which
was Bentley's idea so--but Lee came up
with project raising and then I came up
a solution or easy process raising
months later but together Tech is now a
powerful piece of my life where we get
to get together as project holders and
figure out how can we best create tools
to move forward and people are attracted
to that and we as I said it's evolving
in and of itself then had the idea for
solution raising a few months ago which
is a simple one hour conversation where
we talk for 15 minutes about what it
currently looks like 15 minutes about
our beautiful version of the future and
half an hour talking about we can
actually create in that space with
10,000 people and $100,000 we've had
about 15 today we've tackled food we've
tackled prison we just tackled suicide
tomorrow we're doing self-help industry
some of them are game be more specific
and that's who showed up and other ones
are more my interests and everyone is
come up with a powerful solution but
there are four people coming up with a
solution
how do we then get 10,000 give all the
credit in the world and so figuring out
process raising learning that I can't
map something out not be able to explain
it and expect people to come on board so
instead I try not to do a lot of that
work beforehand and come to a meeting as
a more blank slate feel like what can we
create together and so we're on weak
form of process raising and plane and
attention if not being able to quite
understand each other's vision and yet
we want to create something with 10,000
people on 100
in a solution raising part of it there's
amazingness coming out of it I can every
meeting is just moving it forward but
there was like new tension that comes up
and I don't know what to say except then
back in the fall again don't remember
how her tonight he posted something in
some article and I was like yeah I want
to talk to that person we had a
conversation and that he wanted to start
to make a rural group to practice I make
a rule and I offered to other people and
now there are five of us some people
have come and gone and there are five of
us that are pretty core group that meet
and that was the whole purpose this
practice will make a rule and there's
something amazing coming out of that it
is like the whoo that shall not be named
the God the Son of God that is that was
not the purpose and there's something
beautiful in merging both into the world
and just in our own lives so I have and
then for some reason within this space
every time I feel called to do something
that simply easy cuz that's all I do do
is what it calls to be I can't take on
the complex I don't I'm really pissed
some people off in this space couldn t
like read this I'm like I don't read I'm
like not getting there I don't take
homework from other people I don't do
what is difficult arduous for me I have
to take on one it's what is fun and easy
for me and yet it has been powerful step
forward I take on when there's gross
emotion about someone or some or some
idea I figure out how to learn and grow
from it
my idea has gotten better I have gotten
better I've learned how to play game be
with people and how to play in the
tension of not knowing and not having
the solution and not having the path
laid out and now by version a game be I
still think a technology cooperative is
powerful I still think I'm gonna be
instrumental in healthy and save the
world but in the most ridiculous way
because like oh I don't have to do it I
only have to live my life I have my
version of why game is broken and I
don't think we need to agree on it I
have my version of a utopian future I'm
looking into and I know utopias aren't
possible and so us all holding different
what's wrong with game a and different
what is the beautiful game be we're
living towards that's the first and
second part of solution raising and then
it's just what can we create that
the powerful adjacent possible that we
can fund together and create together
that isn't inflicted on other people
but is a natural attractor that can be
brought in and if we have a process to
do that and it isn't one project it's
every project the dominoes start falling
it's a project that helps people have
autonomy and food and a project that
helps them have access to education with
other public school maybe helps them
have understand their legal system I
mean any project is possible that moves
you forward when you have 10,000 people
and $100,000 I because if I was showing
up in this space I guess I said all of
these things that I kept doing when the
admitted another mala they've reached
out and I said I would try and I don't
feel like I show up very good as a mod
because I can't type out my thoughts and
I can't do conflict resolution if I
can't type out my thoughts my only offer
is like hey you want to have a video
conversation and even then I don't know
if I could be in a role of conflict
resolution unless it's naturally arising
and so I'm on the mod team in this weird
position where I don't like being
leadership over people I don't like
people being in leadership over me I
want to be able to do move forward with
my vision and somehow have it all work
out and it is happening and even being
on the mod team is like me encountering
my issues with leadership my internal
struggles of leadership and moving and
figuring out the learning from that as
well that's the irony that I am the
least I think the least effective mode
on the team that's actually still nod
and yet because Jim's going on
sabbatical I needed someone to do the
the welcome post I offered because I
felt like it was something I could do I
could just copy and paste and do that
once a week but in order to be able to
do that I have to be an admin so I'm not
being made into min which like raises
the even higher in the eyes of the
masses it's what it looks like it has a
little lemon symbol next to it and yet
not being able to show up being
triggered by people who like are waiting
for the leadership to do something both
within the game be Facebook group like
make the rules and enforce the rules and
it feels very parental child and I'm
like that's not how we kraang can be we
need to have like less high
Araki and I'm definitely anti hierarchy
which again he leaned Healy in the
struggle against it instead of like the
beautiful truth inside of it and so the
irony of all of it and just being in
this space and finding what is easy what
is fun what is mine to do has unlike Wow
and doing a lot in this space on what
I'm like on the admitting I have my own
multiple projects that I'm starting some
stuff would not even in game be one of
my coaches had this horrible thing come
out in February started its own Facebook
group it was like a I'll take that on to
let's take on taking down the movie to
move it and pass that off to the people
who are more focused on but you the less
the more I let go of what it needs to
look like the more it happens the more
it weaves together and actually is
coalescing and forming the caterpillar
goo is turning into a butterfly like I'm
the caterpillar Guderian's my own
butterfly but game B is also coalescing
and emerging and the more we need to
name what game a is and name what game B
is and then like map out a path to get
there the less we get to do either of
those things but the more we can hold
our individual versions of what are you
talking can be is with our values
maximized
but honored that we're never going to
get there because utopia is not actually
obtainable and we can agree that game a
is broken and so interconnected that we
might disagree on what the biggest
broken part is but the beauty is we all
get to work on our broken pieces enough
people can agree on a powerful step
forward but they want to take it doesn't
mean everyone has to agree on it and
that's why I'm involved in solutionizing
because it is that it's like well we
could do something with 10,000 people we
don't need all of Canada where I live or
all of the world to agree we just need
10,000 people to get together and agree
that it's something they want and then
to invite the world and it becomes a
very natural attractor so if you're in
the game be space welcomed and find your
people find your Omega roll group
because they're amazing
don't look to leadership because like
you're the leader and I am more
interested in the well I think would be
concerned second tier leadership not the
people on the broad on the that are
interviewed on rebel wisdom not the
people that are interviewed by Joe Rogan
but the people who show up and have
conversations have YouTube channels that
have under 500 subscribers people on
Twitter with with under 500 followers
who are constantly doing their own
personal work the last game be fell
apart because they couldn't decide on
whether you do your own personal
development first or whether you have a
project first and some of us might do
one and some of us might do it the other
but I think the vast majority of us
actually do both inshore woven working
on projects you're gonna come up against
self development stuff or it's gonna
fall apart and doing self development
stuff is actually easier with the
project because it keeps helping you
move forward and so I invite you to come
join game be projects if that's your
thing and you have a project or want to
come and see what other projects are
going on if you want to find people what
a conversation looks like a game be
joined game be conversations but isn't
necessary the place to find someone to
have a conversation but if you reach out
to somebody under there and take them I
guarantee you they'll probably be able
to having a conversation with you if you
if all you want to do is debate on
Facebook that I guess hang out in the
main group type back and forth at each
other but like this is where the magic
happens not here if I'm rebroadcast you
by message to YouTube but in video
conversation in in-person conversation
in plane in the tension and the conflict
of other people not feeling the way you
do of not having a world-changing idea
that everyone's gonna get on board with
and I get to lean it will not want you
to lead it everyone has their own idea
of Gabey everyone has our own idea of
what game is and that is actually game B
that we have seven point five billion
versions of game B and somehow us moving
towards our own individual ones
interweaves our values together to
maximize all of them so we're not
creating utopia or creating proto PIA
please like and
scribe and I'll see you next time let's
get me done more than 200 subscribers or
not I'm continuing on no matter what
thank you